Rubin "Hurricane" Carter Papers MS226
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Rubin "Hurricane" Carter Papers
1995 -- 2009
1950 -- 2014
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Carter, Rubin, 1937-2014
MS226
21.6 Linear Feet
6 Digital Object(s)
Arrangement
This collection is arranged in 9 series: Awards and artifacts; Business and financial records; Clippings, fliers, and programs; Correspondence; Court cases; Photographs; Printed materials; Subject files; and Writings.
Custodial History
This collection was packed by Anne Sauer in May 2013. In November 2014, Sherman Teichman briefly housed the papers, and they were brought to the Tufts Institute for Global Leadership in late November/early December 2015 and transferred to the Digital Collections and Archives.
Scope and Contents
The Rubin "Hurricane" Carter papers consist of Carter's personal papers, including business and financial records; clippings and programs; correspondence; notes, writings, and speeches; extensive subject files; and records of court cases. The collection also includes photographs of Carter and others; numerous awards and honors; and artifacts such as a pair of boxing shorts and a mouth guard sent by a fan. Subject files include memos, agendas, minutes, correspondence, and reports from the Association in Defense of the Wrongly Convicted (AIDWYC). The bulk of the material dates from the mid-1990s through the 2000s, although there are notes, writings, and correspondence dating back to Carter's imprisonment in the 1970s-1980s.
The collection documents Carter's involvement with non-profit legal organizations seeking to exonerate those wrongly convicted, and his career as a motivational speaker and author, as well as his personal life. Subjects include social justice, legal reform, philosophy, and boxing.
Carter suffered a house fire in 2004. Surviving records, particularly the subject files, are smoke damaged and retain the strong scent of deodorizing materials used in post-fire remediation.
Biographical / Historical
Rubin Carter was born on May 6, 1937, in Clifton, New Jersey, to Lloyd and Bertha Carter. At age 14, he was convicted of robbery and assault and sent to the Jamesburg Home for Boys in New Jersey, from which he escaped at age 17 to join the Army. There he took up boxing, and was discharged in 1956. A year later he was convicted of robbery and assault and spent four years in Trenton State Prison. He became a professional boxer on his release in 1961, narrowly losing the World Boxing Association middleweight championship in 1964. Carter and his friend John Artis were arrested in 1966 and charged with committing three murders at the Lafayette Bar in Paterson, New Jersey. Despite inconsistencies in testimony and conflicting evidence, Carter and Artis were found guilty and sentenced to life imprisonment.
While in prison, Carter published The Sixteenth Round: From Number 1 Contender to #45472 (1974). Musician Bob Dylan read the book and visited Carter in prison in 1975, leading to the composition of his song "Hurricane," which raised public awareness of Carter and his case. The two identifying witnesses recanted their testimony, and in March 1976 the New Jersey Supreme Court overturned the convictions of both Artis and Carter. At a second trial in December 1976, prosecutors argued that Carter and Artis were motivated by racial revenge, and they were again convicted and sentenced to life imprisonment. Carter and lead attorney Myron Beldock continued to appeal his conviction with the assistance of members of a Canadian commune. On November 7, 1985, Judge H. Lee Sarokin of the United States District Court in Newark overturned the second conviction and ruled that the prosecutors had withheld evidence and violated the defendants' constitutional rights. Carter was released the next day after a bail hearing.
In 1988, Carter moved to Toronto, Canada. In addition to a career as a popular motivational speaker, he was the Executive Director of the Association in Defense of the Wrongly Convicted from 1993-2004. He worked with the Innocence Project to exonerate the wrongfully convicted and founded Innocence International in 2004. His autobiography, Eye of the Hurricane: My Path from Darkness to Freedom, written with Ken Klonsky, was published in 2011. Carter received numerous awards and honors, including honorary doctorates from Griffith University and York University (2005) and an honorary championship belt from the World Boxing Council (1993). In 1999, a movie was released based on Carter's experiences starring Denzel Washington in the title role, The Hurricane.
Carter married Mae Thelma Basket in 1963, and they had two children, Theodora and Raheem. They were divorced in 1984. Carter was remarried in the 1990s to Canadian commune leader Lisa Peters, whom he later divorced. Carter died on April 20, 2014, in Toronto, of cancer.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Criminal justice, Administration of; Association in Defense of the Wrongly Convicted; Trials (Murder) -- New Jersey -- Paterson; Judicial error -- United States; African American boxers; False imprisonment; Capital punishment -- United States; Prisoners -- United States; Social justice; African American history
- Awards and artifacts, 1989 -- 2012; MS226.001; 10.8 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  Awards consist of the many honors bestowed on Carter from organizations as varied as the U.S. House of Representatives and the House of Commons of Canada to the Bare Knuckle Boxing Hall of Fame. Awards include certificates, plaques, and objects such as globes, clocks, and keys to the city. Artifacts include a pair of boxing shorts and a mouthguard, a yarmulke, pins, a gavel, and paperweights, some sent to Carter by fans.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged in two subseries: 1. Awards; 2. Artifacts.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Awards, 1989 -- 2012; MS226.001.001; 10.8 Linear Feet
    - U.M.A.D.O.P plaque of appreciation, Akron, Ohio, 2001-08-30; MS226.001.001.001.00001 (Box data_value_missing_4f0696a6584067640774aa28075aa367, Box 1)
    - Booker T. Washington Business Association "Education: Each One Teach One" award, Detroit, Michigan, 2001-04-07; MS226.001.001.001.00002 (Box data_value_missing_4f0696a6584067640774aa28075aa367, Box 1)
    - Commemorative plate, Liverpool, England, 2005-11-16; MS226.001.001.001.00003 (Box data_value_missing_4f0696a6584067640774aa28075aa367, Box 1)
    - University of Western Ontario Kinesiology Department Homecoming lecture plaque of appreciation, 1994; MS226.001.001.001.00005 (Box data_value_missing_4f0696a6584067640774aa28075aa367, Box 1)
    - C.A.P.L. Conference plaque of appreciation, Halifax, Nova Scotia, 2000; MS226.001.001.001.00006 (Box data_value_missing_4f0696a6584067640774aa28075aa367, Box 1)
    - Key to the city of San Bernardino, California, 2000-06-16; MS226.001.001.001.00007 (Box data_value_missing_4f0696a6584067640774aa28075aa367, Box 1)
    - Community Living Ontario 50th Anniversary Conference plaque of appreciation, 2003-11; MS226.001.001.001.00008 (Box data_value_missing_4f0696a6584067640774aa28075aa367, Box 1)
    - YMCA Canada Peace Medal certificate, 1999; MS226.001.001.001.00009 (Box data_value_missing_4f0696a6584067640774aa28075aa367, Box 1)
    - Washington D.C. Boxing Hall of Fame certificate, 1990 -- 2009; MS226.001.001.001.00010 (Box data_value_missing_4f0696a6584067640774aa28075aa367, Box 1)
    - BLSAC Windsor award, 1990 -- 2009; MS226.001.001.001.00011 (Box data_value_missing_4f0696a6584067640774aa28075aa367, Box 1)
    - Key to the city of Indianapolis, IN, 1990 -- 2009; MS226.001.001.002.00001 (Box data_value_missing_3e40ca80e019f57ac9e062aa47c2d026, Box 2)
    - Key to the city of Evansville, IN, 1990 -- 2009; MS226.001.001.002.00002 (Box data_value_missing_3e40ca80e019f57ac9e062aa47c2d026, Box 2)
    - Award clock, 1990 -- 2009; MS226.001.001.002.00004 (Box data_value_missing_3e40ca80e019f57ac9e062aa47c2d026, Box 2)
    - Don Mills, CI, appreciation award, 1990 -- 2009; MS226.001.001.002.00005 (Box data_value_missing_3e40ca80e019f57ac9e062aa47c2d026, Box 2)
    - Positive Impact Celebrity Choice award, 2000; MS226.001.001.002.00007 (Box data_value_missing_3e40ca80e019f57ac9e062aa47c2d026, Box 2)
    - Scripter award, 2000-03-04; MS226.001.001.002.00008 (Box data_value_missing_3e40ca80e019f57ac9e062aa47c2d026, Box 2)
    - Institute on Domestic Violence in the African American Community, University of Minnesota, Angel award, 2005-07; MS226.001.001.002.00009 (Box data_value_missing_3e40ca80e019f57ac9e062aa47c2d026, Box 2)
    - Community Partners in Action award, 2000-10-26; MS226.001.001.002.00010 (Box data_value_missing_3e40ca80e019f57ac9e062aa47c2d026, Box 2)
    - African Canadian Achievement Award, Founder's Award, 2004; MS226.001.001.002.00011 (Box data_value_missing_3e40ca80e019f57ac9e062aa47c2d026, Box 2)
    - The Stable A.B.C. Cardiff commemorative obelisk, 2005-11-14; MS226.001.001.002.00013 (Box data_value_missing_3e40ca80e019f57ac9e062aa47c2d026, Box 2)
    - DNA Technology Workshop Thank You globe, MS226.001.001.002.00014 (Box data_value_missing_3e40ca80e019f57ac9e062aa47c2d026, Box 2)
    - Bare Knuckle Boxing Hall of Fame packet, 2012; MS226.001.001.013.00063 (Box data_value_missing_4f0696a6584067640774aa28075aa367, Box 13)
    - Canadian Boxing Hall of Fame Membership certificates, 1994; MS226.001.001.013.00064 (Box data_value_missing_4f0696a6584067640774aa28075aa367, Box 13)
    - Congressional Recognition certificate, 2004; MS226.001.001.013.00065 (Box data_value_missing_4f0696a6584067640774aa28075aa367, Box 13)
    - House of Commons, Canada, African Canadian Achievement Founder's Award, 2004; MS226.001.001.013.00066 (Box data_value_missing_4f0696a6584067640774aa28075aa367, Box 13)
    - Northeastern University student group awards, 2001; MS226.001.001.013.00067 (Box data_value_missing_4f0696a6584067640774aa28075aa367, Box 13)
    - San Francisco Proclamation of commendation, 2000; MS226.001.001.013.00068 (Box data_value_missing_4f0696a6584067640774aa28075aa367, Box 13)
    - Canadian Boxing Hall of Fame plaque, 1990 -- 2009; MS226.001.001.014.00001 (Box data_value_missing_3e40ca80e019f57ac9e062aa47c2d026, Box 14)
    - Northeastern University John D. O'Bryant African American Institute L.I.F.E. award clock, 2001-05-02; MS226.001.001.014.00002 (Box data_value_missing_3e40ca80e019f57ac9e062aa47c2d026, Box 14)
    - New Jersey Juvenile Justice Commission plaque of appreciation, 2004-11-04; MS226.001.001.014.00003 (Box data_value_missing_3e40ca80e019f57ac9e062aa47c2d026, Box 14)
    - University of South Florida plaque of appreciation, 2001-03-01; MS226.001.001.014.00004 (Box data_value_missing_3e40ca80e019f57ac9e062aa47c2d026, Box 14)
    - Ohio State University Medical Center plaque of appreciation, 2005-02-21; MS226.001.001.014.00005 (Box data_value_missing_3e40ca80e019f57ac9e062aa47c2d026, Box 14)
    - Provisional Accelerated Learning Center plaque of appreciation, 2000-06-16; MS226.001.001.014.00006 (Box data_value_missing_3e40ca80e019f57ac9e062aa47c2d026, Box 14)
    - Key to the city of Canastota, New York, 1989-06-10; MS226.001.001.014.00007 (Box data_value_missing_3e40ca80e019f57ac9e062aa47c2d026, Box 14)
    - JUSTICEwa Ambassador plaque, Perth, 2010-02; MS226.001.001.014.00008 (Box data_value_missing_3e40ca80e019f57ac9e062aa47c2d026, Box 14)
    - Columbus, Ohio, Office of the Mayor Proclamation, 2005; MS226.001.001.015.00001 (Box data_value_missing_0528436d08824cc30c17cc57fc820553, Box 15)
    - Des Moines certificate of appreciation, 2000-03-07; MS226.001.001.015.00002 (Box data_value_missing_0528436d08824cc30c17cc57fc820553, Box 15)
    - Minneapolis Proclamation, 2005; MS226.001.001.015.00003 (Box data_value_missing_0528436d08824cc30c17cc57fc820553, Box 15)
    - Griffith University, admission to the Degree of the Doctor of University citation, 2003; MS226.001.001.015.00004 (Box data_value_missing_0528436d08824cc30c17cc57fc820553, Box 15)
    - San Bernardino County Resolution, 2000; MS226.001.001.015.00005 (Box data_value_missing_0528436d08824cc30c17cc57fc820553, Box 15)
  - Artifacts, 1989 -- 2011; MS226.001.002; 10.8 Linear Feet
    - Gavel, 1990 -- 2009; MS226.001.002.001.00004 (Box data_value_missing_4f0696a6584067640774aa28075aa367, Box 1)
    - International Transfers International globe, 2003; MS226.001.002.002.00003 (Box data_value_missing_3e40ca80e019f57ac9e062aa47c2d026, Box 2)
    - East York Schools paperweight, 1990 -- 2009; MS226.001.002.002.00006 (Box data_value_missing_3e40ca80e019f57ac9e062aa47c2d026, Box 2)
    - University of South Florida star paperweight, 2001; MS226.001.002.002.00012 (Box data_value_missing_3e40ca80e019f57ac9e062aa47c2d026, Box 2)
    - Correspondence accompanying shorts and mouthpiece, 2011; MS226.001.002.016.00001 (Box data_value_missing_0528436d08824cc30c17cc57fc820553, Box 16)
    - Shorts and mouthpiece, 2011; MS226.001.002.016.00002 (Box data_value_missing_0528436d08824cc30c17cc57fc820553, Box 16)
    - Pins, 1990 -- 2009; MS226.001.002.016.00004 (Box data_value_missing_0528436d08824cc30c17cc57fc820553, Box 16)
    - Yarmulke from the wedding of Barbara and Michael, 1989-08-24; MS226.001.002.016.00005 (Box data_value_missing_0528436d08824cc30c17cc57fc820553, Box 16)
- Business and financial records, 1980 -- 2013; MS226.002; 3.6 Linear Feet
  Carter's business and financial records document his career as a motivational speaker, author, consultant, and prisoner advocate. Records include contracts, correspondence, meeting notes, proposals, royalty statements, scripts and transcripts for television appearances, and travel plans and agendas.
  Records are arranged alphabetically by subject and then chronologically.
  - AIDWYC emails, 2002; MS226.002.005.00001 (Box data_value_missing_1bf3371db5f8b81073905786da8bc3f8, Box 5)
  - American Program Bureau contract, 1999; MS226.002.005.00002 (Box data_value_missing_1bf3371db5f8b81073905786da8bc3f8, Box 5)
  - Authors' Marketing Services blurb and Three Star Security correspondence, 2005; MS226.002.005.00003 (Box data_value_missing_1bf3371db5f8b81073905786da8bc3f8, Box 5)
  - Business cards, 1980 -- 2009; MS226.002.005.00004 (Box data_value_missing_1bf3371db5f8b81073905786da8bc3f8, Box 5)
  - Business correspondence, 1995; MS226.002.005.00005 (Box data_value_missing_1bf3371db5f8b81073905786da8bc3f8, Box 5)
  - Business correspondence, 1996 -- 1997; MS226.002.005.00006 (Box data_value_missing_1bf3371db5f8b81073905786da8bc3f8, Box 5)
  - Business correspondence, 1999 -- 2000; MS226.002.005.00007 (Box data_value_missing_1bf3371db5f8b81073905786da8bc3f8, Box 5)
  - Business correspondence, 2001 -- 2002; MS226.002.005.00008 (Box data_value_missing_1bf3371db5f8b81073905786da8bc3f8, Box 5)
  - Business correspondence, 2003 -- 2004; MS226.002.005.00009 (Box data_value_missing_1bf3371db5f8b81073905786da8bc3f8, Box 5)
  - Business correspondence, 2003 -- 2004; MS226.002.005.00010 (Box data_value_missing_1bf3371db5f8b81073905786da8bc3f8, Box 5)
  - Business correspondence sent, 2004; MS226.002.005.00011 (Box data_value_missing_1bf3371db5f8b81073905786da8bc3f8, Box 5)
  - Business correspondence and summary of accounts, 2004 -- 2005; MS226.002.005.00012 (Box data_value_missing_1bf3371db5f8b81073905786da8bc3f8, Box 5)
  - Business correspondence, 2006 -- 2007; MS226.002.005.00013 (Box data_value_missing_1bf3371db5f8b81073905786da8bc3f8, Box 5)
  - Business correspondence, 2009 -- 2011; MS226.002.005.00014 (Box data_value_missing_1bf3371db5f8b81073905786da8bc3f8, Box 5)
  - Business correspondence, 2012 -- 2013; MS226.002.005.00015 (Box data_value_missing_1bf3371db5f8b81073905786da8bc3f8, Box 5)
  - CCLA meeting notes, 1998; MS226.002.005.00016 (Box data_value_missing_1bf3371db5f8b81073905786da8bc3f8, Box 5)
  - Contracts, 1994 -- 1995; MS226.002.005.00017 (Box data_value_missing_1bf3371db5f8b81073905786da8bc3f8, Box 5)
  - Contracts and licenses, 2002 -- 2006; MS226.002.005.00018 (Box data_value_missing_1bf3371db5f8b81073905786da8bc3f8, Box 5)
  - Contracts pending, 2004 -- 2005; MS226.002.005.00019 (Box data_value_missing_1bf3371db5f8b81073905786da8bc3f8, Box 5)
  - Contracts waiting for payment, 2004 -- 2005; MS226.002.005.00020 (Box data_value_missing_1bf3371db5f8b81073905786da8bc3f8, Box 5)
  - Contracts, 2009; MS226.002.005.00021 (Box data_value_missing_1bf3371db5f8b81073905786da8bc3f8, Box 5)
  - Correspondence with Doug Tjapkes of Innocent!, 2005; MS226.002.005.00022 (Box data_value_missing_1bf3371db5f8b81073905786da8bc3f8, Box 5)
  - Eye of the Hurricane book tour agenda, 2010; MS226.002.005.00023 (Box data_value_missing_1bf3371db5f8b81073905786da8bc3f8, Box 5)
  - The Innocents proposal, 2004; MS226.002.005.00024 (Box data_value_missing_1bf3371db5f8b81073905786da8bc3f8, Box 5)
  - The Innocents voice over script and correspondence, 2008; MS226.002.005.00025 (Box data_value_missing_1bf3371db5f8b81073905786da8bc3f8, Box 5)
  - Larry King - Rubin Carter transcript, 2000; MS226.002.005.00026 (Box data_value_missing_1bf3371db5f8b81073905786da8bc3f8, Box 5)
  - Overview of proposed documentary, 2007; MS226.002.005.00027 (Box data_value_missing_1bf3371db5f8b81073905786da8bc3f8, Box 5)
  - Program corporation of America case, 2004; MS226.002.005.00028 (Box data_value_missing_1bf3371db5f8b81073905786da8bc3f8, Box 5)
  - Royalty statements, 2003 -- 2004; MS226.002.005.00029 (Box data_value_missing_1bf3371db5f8b81073905786da8bc3f8, Box 5)
  - Travel plans and agenda, 2004; MS226.002.005.00030 (Box data_value_missing_1bf3371db5f8b81073905786da8bc3f8, Box 5)
  - "Vindicated" television show proposal, 2000; MS226.002.005.00031 (Box data_value_missing_1bf3371db5f8b81073905786da8bc3f8, Box 5)
- Clippings, fliers, and programs, 1964 -- 2011; MS226.003; 3.6 Linear Feet
  Clippings, fliers, and programs consist of articles in newspapers, magazines, and other publications on topics in which Carter had an interest, and fliers and programs from events he attended, including boxing matches, the Academy Awards, and speaking occasions.
  Arranged chronologically.
  - Clippings, 1964; MS226.003.003.00001 (Box data_value_missing_1bf3371db5f8b81073905786da8bc3f8, Box 3)
  - Clippings, 1976; MS226.003.003.00002 (Box data_value_missing_1bf3371db5f8b81073905786da8bc3f8, Box 3)
  - Clippings, 1988; MS226.003.003.00003 (Box data_value_missing_1bf3371db5f8b81073905786da8bc3f8, Box 3)
  - Clippings, 1992; MS226.003.003.00004 (Box data_value_missing_1bf3371db5f8b81073905786da8bc3f8, Box 3)
  - Clippings and programs, 1993; MS226.003.003.00005 (Box data_value_missing_1bf3371db5f8b81073905786da8bc3f8, Box 3)
  - Clippings and programs, 1994; MS226.003.003.00006 (Box data_value_missing_1bf3371db5f8b81073905786da8bc3f8, Box 3)
  - Clippings and programs, 1995; MS226.003.003.00007 (Box data_value_missing_1bf3371db5f8b81073905786da8bc3f8, Box 3)
  - Clippings and programs, 1996; MS226.003.003.00008 (Box data_value_missing_1bf3371db5f8b81073905786da8bc3f8, Box 3)
  - Clippings and programs, 1997; MS226.003.003.00009 (Box data_value_missing_1bf3371db5f8b81073905786da8bc3f8, Box 3)
  - Clippings, 1998; MS226.003.003.00010 (Box data_value_missing_1bf3371db5f8b81073905786da8bc3f8, Box 3)
  - Clippings and programs, 1999; MS226.003.003.00011 (Box data_value_missing_1bf3371db5f8b81073905786da8bc3f8, Box 3)
  - Clippings, programs, and fliers (1 of 2), 2000; MS226.003.003.00012 (Box data_value_missing_1bf3371db5f8b81073905786da8bc3f8, Box 3)
  - Clippings, programs, and fliers (2 of 2), 2000; MS226.003.003.00013 (Box data_value_missing_1bf3371db5f8b81073905786da8bc3f8, Box 3)
  - Clippings, programs, and fliers, 2001; MS226.003.003.00014 (Box data_value_missing_1bf3371db5f8b81073905786da8bc3f8, Box 3)
  - Clippings and programs, 2002; MS226.003.003.00015 (Box data_value_missing_1bf3371db5f8b81073905786da8bc3f8, Box 3)
  - Clippings, 2003; MS226.003.003.00016 (Box data_value_missing_1bf3371db5f8b81073905786da8bc3f8, Box 3)
  - Clippings, 2004; MS226.003.003.00017 (Box data_value_missing_1bf3371db5f8b81073905786da8bc3f8, Box 3)
  - Clippings and programs (1 of 2), 2005; MS226.003.003.00018 (Box data_value_missing_1bf3371db5f8b81073905786da8bc3f8, Box 3)
  - Clippings and programs (2 of 2), 2005; MS226.003.003.00019 (Box data_value_missing_1bf3371db5f8b81073905786da8bc3f8, Box 3)
  - Clippings and programs, 2006; MS226.003.003.00020 (Box data_value_missing_1bf3371db5f8b81073905786da8bc3f8, Box 3)
  - Programs, 2007; MS226.003.003.00021 (Box data_value_missing_1bf3371db5f8b81073905786da8bc3f8, Box 3)
  - Clippings and programs, 2008; MS226.003.003.00022 (Box data_value_missing_1bf3371db5f8b81073905786da8bc3f8, Box 3)
  - Clippings, 2009; MS226.003.003.00023 (Box data_value_missing_1bf3371db5f8b81073905786da8bc3f8, Box 3)
  - Clippings, 2011; MS226.003.003.00024 (Box data_value_missing_1bf3371db5f8b81073905786da8bc3f8, Box 3)
  - Clippings and programs, 1990 -- 2009; MS226.003.003.00025 (Box data_value_missing_1bf3371db5f8b81073905786da8bc3f8, Box 3)
- Correspondence, 1983 -- 2013; MS226.004; 7.2 Linear Feet
  The bulk of Carter's correspondence is fan mail, detailing his influence on hundreds of correspondents from many countries. There is also some personal correspondence with friends and family, and an incomplete run of telephone message books dating from 2008-2011. Some correspondence is unopened. Please consult an archivist regarding access to unopened materials. Many fans sent Carter financial contributions, which have been removed. Gifts that fans sent Carter, such as CDs, DVDs, and books, were left in place. Business correspondence may be found in series 2, business and financial records.
  Correspondence is arranged alphabetically and then chronologically.
  - Correspondence - needs response (1 of 4), 2000 -- 2001; MS226.004.003.00026 (Box data_value_missing_1bf3371db5f8b81073905786da8bc3f8, Box 3)
  - Correspondence - needs response (2 of 4), 2000 -- 2001; MS226.004.003.00027 (Box data_value_missing_1bf3371db5f8b81073905786da8bc3f8, Box 3)
  - Correspondence - needs response (3 of 4), 2000 -- 2001; MS226.004.003.00028 (Box data_value_missing_1bf3371db5f8b81073905786da8bc3f8, Box 3)
  - Correspondence - needs response (4 of 4), 2000 -- 2001; MS226.004.003.00029 (Box data_value_missing_1bf3371db5f8b81073905786da8bc3f8, Box 3)
  - Fan mail (1 of 3), 1994 -- 2002; MS226.004.003.00030 (Box data_value_missing_1bf3371db5f8b81073905786da8bc3f8, Box 3)
  - Fan mail (2 of 3), 1994 -- 2002; MS226.004.003.00031 (Box data_value_missing_1bf3371db5f8b81073905786da8bc3f8, Box 3)
  - Fan mail (3 of 3), 1994 -- 2002; MS226.004.003.00032 (Box data_value_missing_1bf3371db5f8b81073905786da8bc3f8, Box 3)
  - Fan mail, 1996 -- 2003; MS226.004.003.00033 (Box data_value_missing_1bf3371db5f8b81073905786da8bc3f8, Box 3)
  - Fan mail, 2000 -- 2003; MS226.004.003.00034 (Box data_value_missing_1bf3371db5f8b81073905786da8bc3f8, Box 3)
  - Fan mail, 2000 -- 2013; MS226.004.004 (Box data_value_missing_1bf3371db5f8b81073905786da8bc3f8, Box 4)
  - Letters from juvenile facilities, 2004 -- 2009; MS226.004.005.00032 (Box data_value_missing_1bf3371db5f8b81073905786da8bc3f8, Box 5)
  - Letters from school children, 2001; MS226.004.005.00033 (Box data_value_missing_1bf3371db5f8b81073905786da8bc3f8, Box 5)
  - Letters from school children, 2002; MS226.004.005.00034 (Box data_value_missing_1bf3371db5f8b81073905786da8bc3f8, Box 5)
  - Letters from school children, 2003; MS226.004.005.00035 (Box data_value_missing_1bf3371db5f8b81073905786da8bc3f8, Box 5)
  - Letters from school children, 2006 -- 2007; MS226.004.005.00036 (Box data_value_missing_1bf3371db5f8b81073905786da8bc3f8, Box 5)
  - Letters from school children, 2012; MS226.004.005.00037 (Box data_value_missing_1bf3371db5f8b81073905786da8bc3f8, Box 5)
  - Personal correspondence, 1983; MS226.004.005.00038 (Box data_value_missing_1bf3371db5f8b81073905786da8bc3f8, Box 5)